Open door
Pick up bowl
Put away bowl
Put away pan
Pick up mug
Turn on tap
Wash mug
Put down mug
Pick up sponge
Wet sponge
Dry sponge
Put soap on sponge
Clean mug
Put down mug
Clean another mug
Scrub mug
Scrub handle
Put down mug
Pick up bowl
Scrub bowl
Scrub underside of bowl
Put down bowl
Pick up spoon
Scrub spoon
Put down spoon
Pick up spoon
Scrub spoon
Pick up bowl
Scrub plate
Put down plate
Pick up glass
Scrub glass
Scrub inside glass
Put down glass
Pick up another glass
Scrub glass
Scrub inside glass
put down sponge
put down glass
pick up Tupperware lids
scrub Tupperware lids
put down Tupperware lids
pick up Tupperware
pre-wash Tupperware
scrub Tupperware
put down sponge
rinse Tupperware
put Tupperware on drying rack
rinse mug
put mug on drying rack
pick up mug
rinse mug
Put mug on drying rack
Pour water out of glass
Rinse glass
Pick up spoon
Rinse spoon
Pick up bowel
Rinse bowel
Put down bowel
Pick up glass
Rinse glass
Put down glass
Pick up lid
Wash lid
Put down lid
Rinse plate
Put down plate
Dry off hands
[END SUBTITLE]